newsday.co.tt 2019-11-12

# Privacy Policy - Trinidad and Tobago Newsday

Your privacy is important to us. It is Daily News Limited's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, https://newsday.co.tt

We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you which is infrequent. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.

We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.

We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.

We use third-party services provided by [Google](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=ZZ) for analytics and serving ads on our website and [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/full_data_use_policy) for managing article comments.

**Google Analytics**

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our website. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

**Google AdSense**

Google AdSense allows publishers in the Google Network of content sites to serve automatic text, image, video, or interactive media advertisements, that are targeted to site content and audience. These advertisements are administered, sorted, and maintained by Google.

Personal information like your name, email address, phone number and full address are not collected by Google Analytics or Google AdSense. Google may use your IP address and location to provide information in Google Analytics and Google AdSense. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>

If you wish, you can opt-out of having made your activity on our website available to Google Analytics by installing the [Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about your activity.

**Facebook Comments**

The Facebook Comments Plugin lets people comment on content on our site using their Facebook account. People can choose to share their comment activity with their friends (and friends of their friends) on Facebook as well. We do not retrieve data from your Facebook Account for our own use.

Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.

You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.

Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us at [socialmedia@newsday.co.tt](mailto:socialmedia@newsday.co.tt)
